

MARK PHAYTA

DIGITAL CREATIVE DIRECTOR | DIGITAL MARKETING MANAGER | WEB-DESIGNER

DOB: 31.8.1984 POB: U.S.A.

With 8 years of experience in the Digital world with the role of various parts from Webmaster, Web-Designer, Interactive Specialist, and Digital Marketing; I had never felt to stop learning new things in the Digital world. Being an Objective-Oriented person, I feel that it's a fascinating challenge to find solutions for different tasks. From doing Gallup's Strength Finder, my 5 top strengths are Command, Ideation, Activator, Futuristic, and Relator.

find out more about me here...

(f) www.facebook.com/markiez.trance (iii) www.portfolios.net/profile/markiez

Education

2001 to 2005 Sirindhorn International Institute of Technology

(Thammasat University)

Field of Study: Engineering Management

1994 to 2001 Ekamai International School

Qualification: Highshool Diploma

1991 to 1994 Bangkok Patana School

Working Experience

Jan 2014 to Present

AIA Thailand

Digital Marketing Manager

Current Salary: 84,000 Baht

Achievements:

- 1. Implementation of Lead Management System
- 2. Digital Transformation
- 3. Launch of Facebook
- 4. Launch new sales tool

Key Responsibilities:

Number of Subordinates: 3

- 1. Lead & Sales Generation
- 2. Construct & Develop Digital Marketing Strategies
- 3. Create, Track, and Optimize campaigns
- 4. Digital platform initiatives and support across organization
- 5. Monitor and Respond to Corporate Social Medias

Jun 2010 to Dec 2013

Wall Street Institute

Digital Creative Director / Creative Director (Last Position)

Achievements:

- 1. Increased digital conversion rates 10x
- 2. Integrated Marketing Campaign Launch
- 3. Launch new sales tool

Key Responsibilities:

Number of Subordinates: 5

- 1. Integrate Marketing strategies
- 2. Direct Campaign / Design / Multimedia creation
- 3. Support Lead & Sales Generation medias
- 4. Brand building
- 5. Digital Marketing initiatives

Jan 2010 to May 2010

SF Cinema City

Web-Designer

Key Responsibilities:

- 1. Website & Media design
- 2. Campaign creation
- 3. Mobile Application design



Working Experience

May 2009 to Dec 2010

Standard Chartered Bank (Thailand)

Website Director / Online Project Manager

Achievements:

- 1. Customer-Centric web tools
- 2. Live Fx web tool

Key Responsibilities:

- 1. Maintain country website
- 2. Content creation
- 3. Website tools initiatives
- 4. Consultant for 5 countries of SCBT
- 5. New media initiatives

Feb 2009 to May 2009

University of the Thai Chamber of Commerce

Website Director / Online Project Manager

Key Responsibilities:

- 1. Maintain website
- 2. Content creation
- 3. Website tools initiatives
- 4. New media initiatives
- 5. Website design

Sep 2007 to Feb 2009

Inspire Entertainment

Website Director / Online Editor

Achievements:

- 1. Launch of 12 websites
- 2. Increased web traffic 2x

Key Responsibilities:

Number of Subordinates: 5

Number of Subordinates: 3

- 1. Direct website designs and mechanics
- 2. Content creation
- 3. Campaign creation
- 4. Content planning
- 5. Digital Marketing planning
- 6. Strategic solutions for clients / sponsors

Websites:

www.fhm.in.th

www.arenamagazine.in.th

www.carmagazine.in.th

www.stuff.in.th

www.cawaii.in.th

www.rav.in.th

www.casaviva.in.th

www.hehe55.in.th

www.entertainweekly.in.th

www.musicexpress.in.th

www.siambanterng.in.th

www.missteenthailand.com

www.travelthai.in.th

www.zoo.in.th

Apr 2005 to Aug 2007

Sony Device Thailand

Production Planner

Key Responsibilities:

- 1. Production planning
- 2. Resource management
- 3. Website production

More about me...

Skills		Interests	
Language	English / Thai	WebsitesDesignOnline CommunityEvents/Party	Social MediaMobileMusicSci-Fi Movies
Computer	Ps Photoshop		
	Ai Illustrator		
	Dw Dreamweaver	Ranking	
	FI Flash	DesignCrowd #662 (out of 175,209 Designers)	

Gallup Strength Finder

Command

People strong in the Command theme have presence. They can take control of a situation and make decisions.

Ideation

People strong in the Ideation theme are fascinated by ideas. They are able to find connections between seemingly disparate phenomena.

Activator

People strong in the Activator theme can make things happen by turning thoughts into action. They are often impatient.

Futuristic

People strong in the Futuristic theme are inspired by the future and what could be. They inspire others with their visions of the future.

Relator

People who are strong in the Relator theme enjoy close relationships with others. They find deep satisfaction in working hard with friends to achieve a goal.

Projects

BB Clinic (204 to 2015)

Digital and Social Media Consultant and Leads Generations (Increased sales 5x)

BRAND'S ® Essence of Chicken (2012)

Mother's Day Digital Campaign - Digital Creative Director

Perfect Property (2012 to 2013)

Website & Digital Advertising Designs

Krungsri Auto (2012 to 2013)

E-mail Marketing Designs

Yayoi (2012 to 2013)

Digital and Social Media Consultant and Production Lead